Guide to the Victor Rabinowitz Papers TAM.123
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Records of the Louis M. Rabinowitz Foundation, 1954-1991.
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: RO-RU, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: S-SC, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: SE-SL, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: SO-SP, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: ST-SU, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: T, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: U, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: V, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: W-WB, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: WE, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: WH-WI, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: WO, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: X-Z, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1950, 1955-1958 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous (I), 1972 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous (II), 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous (I), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous (II), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous (III), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous (I), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Inquiries/Miscellaneous (II), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: A, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: B, 1967, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: C-CE, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: CI-CO, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: E, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: F, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: G, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: H, 1973-1974, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: I, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: J, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: K, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: L, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: M, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: N, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: O, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: P, 1973-1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: R, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: S, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: T, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: U, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: V, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Rejections: W-Z, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Financial, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Financial, 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Financial, 1978-1984 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Financial: Audit Materials, 1944, 1960-1976 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) File, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Keeney, Mary Jane: Will, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: Advisory Board, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 31)